atoot.com 2014-04-06

# Our Privacy Policy : Marriage Compatibility : Palm Reading : Love Compatibility : Atoot.com

Atoot.com is a Traditional Sciences Portal. At Atoot.com, we are committed to taking your privacy very seriously abide by the following policy to ensure your satisfaction.

  * 1\. What information does Atoot.com collect/track about me?

Atoot.com offers very personalized content and service that may require personal information like Date of Birth, Time of Birth and Location of Birth of its members. General Public (other members, visitors, people not affiliated with Atoot.com, financial institutions used to process payments) cannot use this information. Additionally, this personalized information is only required from those seeking personalized content, and not from other visitors, who may browse, search non-personalized content without submitting this information. Any financial information provided by you (credit card number, etc.) will not be stored by Atoot.com and hence, cannot be shared or provided to anyone.

Certain generic information that cannot be used to identify a person (including username, sun sign, geographical data) may be shown in the user profile, especially when related to forum postings, etc.

  * 2\. What does Atoot.com do with the information it collects/tracks?

Atoot.com collects information from our users primarily to ensure that we are able to fulfill your requirements and to deliver personalized experience.

  * 3\. With whom is the collected information shared?

Certain personal information like Birth information, etc. may be shared with affiliates to allow creation of personalized content and service for you. No financial data is preserved or shared at Atoot.com

  * 4\. What is your policy on updating or deleting personal information?

Personal information may easily be updated from the “My Profile” page after you have logged in.

  * 5\. Tell me about security of my personal information

Atoot.com takes every precaution to protect your information, both online and offline. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us. All your information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. We use the best industry standards to secure your sensitive financial information, which is not stored by us, and is handled by the secure financial institutions only. 

  * 6\. Tell me about sms/e-mail subscription and opt-out policy

Atoot.com provides several sms and email subscription options to its visitors and members. Recipients can unsubscribe to the service either through this website, or using the link provided at the bottom of the email. If you ever have a problem with your subscription, feel free to contact our team.

  * 7\. How do I contact Atoot.com?

Please contact us through the Contact Us page.
